quiz_data = [
    {
        "question": "What port does POP3 operate on?",
        "correct_answer": "110",
        "options": ["139", "112", "110", "120"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What port does SMTP operate on?",
        "correct_answer": "25",
        "options": ["125", "143", "25", "161"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What port does Telnet run from?",
        "correct_answer": "23",
        "options": ["22", "23", "21", "25"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What port does SNMP use?",
        "correct_answer": "161",
        "options": ["425", "139", "161", "162"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What service runs off port 135?",
        "correct_answer": "EPMAP",
        "options": ["EPMAP", "NetBIOS-ns", "NetBIOS-ssn", "IMAP"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What port does ISO-TSAP operate on?",
        "correct_answer": "102",
        "options": ["141", "102", "113", "161"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What service runs off port 139?",
        "correct_answer": "NetBIOS-ssn",
        "options": ["EPMAP", "NetBIOS-ns", "NetBIOS-ssn", "IMAP"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What port does SNMP use?",
        "correct_answer": "161",
        "options": ["135", "141", "161", "162"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What service operates on port 143?",
        "correct_answer": "IMAP",
        "options": ["EPMAP", "NetBIOS-ns", "NetBIOS-ssn", "IMAP"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What port does SMTPS operate?",
        "correct_answer": "465",
        "options": ["464", "465", "466", "425"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which service uses TCP 2049?",
        "correct_answer": "NFS",
        "options": ["MySQL", "NFS", "Microsoft SQL", "VNC"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What port does FTP command control use?",
        "correct_answer": "21",
        "options": ["19", "22", "21", "20"]
    }
]
